We will be filming with the cooperation of Yukaeru Resort Gero-Registration.
Thank you very much for allowing us to film on location.
Thank you very much.
Here we go!
This is Hanaka Akimoto and Nao Sakura.
I'm Hanaka Akimoto and Nao Sakura. We'd like to go on location with you today.
We've already enjoyed the Giro and other techniques.
Shouldn't we bring back some souvenirs? I guess so.
The perfect place to get souvenirs is Ideyu morning market.
It opens at 8:00 a.m. Let's take a look at the souvenirs here.
I'd like to. I'm off then.
Knock-knock, knock-knock.
What do they have here?
There's really a lot of stuff here.
I want to see it.
Is this what a jellyfish looks like? Originally.
Yes, it is.
It's very modish, isn't it?
It's black and white and matte.
It's very mode.
Dad would love the horseradish seeds.
Really? You like it?
Oh, shiitake tea?
You want some shiitake tea? I do.
Do you want some?
Salted tomato and sweet soybeans.
I want to try it.
It's so good!
I'll buy it.
Can I buy some? More and more!
Thank you very much.
Please.
Are these shiitake mushrooms from the Shiitake Gif?
It says so.
Thank you very much.
Please wait.
I got salted tomatoes and sweet soybeans.
I'll put sweet soybeans on it.
It's called "Fruberry".
Fruberry?
Want to try some?
May I?
Mushy.
Yeah, it's delicious!
It's like all the flavor is concentrated.
Delicious!
What is this?
It's called "yama-kurage.
Mountain jellyfish?
Wow, I've never seen it before.
What's a mountain jellyfish?
Lettuce.
Lettuce?
Oh, really?
Wow.
May I taste it?
Oh, really?
Bon appétit!
This one is from the nest, and that one is from Kim Pry.
Oh, they're different.
The texture is...
Yum!
Delicious. Oh, lettuce?
Lettuce?
Tastes like leaves.
Tastes like lettuce.
It's delicious.
You can use it today in water, in stir-fries, stews, all kinds of things.
Mmm.
Oh, I love red turnips!
Oh, I love this one.
I love sour ones.
Oh, I see, thank you very much!
Delicious!
Red turnip
Bon appétit!
Fresh taste
Delicious!
I'll have this one, please.
Thank you very much.
There's a fortune for you.
Do you want to try fortune-telling?
I want to try fortune-telling!
Let's try.
I haven't drawn a fortune this year.
Oh, really?
Maybe.
I did.
How was it?How was it?
It was good luck.
It was a good day?
Are you sure you don't want me to repaint it?
It's not like we're repainting it or anything.
It's not a repaint.
This is the fortune here.
Yeah.
Well, well, well.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
100 yen, please.
I'm so excited.
Ah!
Kichi kichi.
Exquisite.
Kichi kichi
I am...
A shallow river is deep enough to cross
When you cross a shallow river with your neck in the water, you'll find yourself in a big deep river.
Now is the time of good fortune.
If you cross the world without letting your guard down, your work will go well
So they say.
Oh...
Well, then...
You're saying that I shouldn't be so optimistic.
That's right.
I understand.
I'm in no rush. I'm in no rush. I'm taking my time with my current work.
Oh...
But if I don't rush, new luck will start to move in.
And I'll be blessed with money as well.
That's great.
Isn't it good?
But only if we don't rush.
Don't be in a hurry.
I'm in no hurry.
I'll just bluff now.
You've never been in a hurry before.
I don't know.
Just leave it at that, okay?
Yes!
Have you ever been in a hurry?
Yes, I have.
Oh!
Let's take a closer look.
I was wondering what that smoke was.
Steam.
I'm gonna buy this.
I can't save it
The most delicious hot spring man in all of porn.
Really?
Can I eat it?
Can I?
It's a little higher quality, but it's delicious.
Oh, it's delicious.
I just have one of these.
Yes, sir.
Can I have two then?
Yes, please.
Yes, 180 yen.
Thank you very much.
May I? Thank you.
Wow.
Cute size.
One bite.
What? It's just a bite, right?
Anko (red bean paste) is all over the place!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It's a good morning sugar.
What are you doing?
I'm making a planter.
Oh, that.
It's going to be used to put flowers in.
Oh, I see.
Now you're making a fire.
Yes, to burn it.
Why are you burning it?
When you burn it, it turns black and turns to charcoal.
It keeps the bones from rotting.
I see.
I don't know...
That's interesting.
I didn't know that.
How about your souvenirs, Hou-san?
I bought a lot of things!
It's great!It's great.
No, it's morning. It feels good.
I miss it.
Hey, the kids are participating.
Attendance is amazing.
Hey.
Thank you very much.
Oh, Dad! That feels good!
Second place in radio calisthenics!
Second place!
That's great!
I'm impressed that all the staff and customers are doing it.
It's amazing! Do you do this exercise every morning?
Since last year.
Since last year!
I think this morning market starts at 8:00 a.m. What time does it start?
8:00 a.m.
At 8 in the morning! So this is how it starts!
It's so nice!
I'll be back!
I would love to have you!
Thank you very much!
Here are our reflection pictures this time!
It was delicious!
It was delicious! Each one a little different.
Different from each other
With the buns
I think I got some good pictures!
Iteyu morning market!
It's been about last year, the Corona disaster has come back again.
The daily life is back, and the customers are coming back.
Father also said that the smiles are increasing!
Please come to Iteyu Asaichi Gero!
I want you all to come to Iteyu Asaichi Gero and participate in the radio calisthenics!
We can all do the exercises together in the morning.
It's a rare opportunity! A place like this
It's a great place with a very warm atmosphere.
We hope to come back again!
Please come to this place!
Come and visit us!
It was a great school!
Bye bye! We'll have more fun after this!
It's time for Orca News!
We are Orca, and we will release our 2nd EP on June 28th!
We are going to release our 2nd EP on June 28th!
Our 2nd EP!
This time, all songs are collaborated with Kenta Matsuguma!
That's right! The music!
Isn't it strong already?
No, really.
The words are strong!
We've had a lot of different songs written.
The combination of Matsukuma's verses and Shachi's verses is really good.
We've created new songs that we've never had before.
Please check them out!
And we, Team Shachi, are now
We are now doing free live!
We are touring various places!
Not only live concerts but also special benefit events will be held.
We hope you will come and see us!
Please come and see us!
That's all for now, Orca News!
Bye bye!